Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series CX is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series CXI is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series CXII is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series CXIII is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series CX. PIGGYBACK SERVICE
  - Sub-Series 534-0. Piggyback Service. General
    - General, 1956-1961 (Box 627b, Folder 1)
      August 1956-March 15, 1961.
    - Replies to Circular Letter Dated May 1, 1956, 1956-1957 (Box 627b, Folder 2)
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad, 1956 (Box 627b, Folder 3)
    - General, 1955-1956 (Box 627b, Folder 4)
      November 1955-July 1956.
    - General, 1953-1955 (Box 627b, Folder 5)
      1953-October 1955.
- Series CXI. TRACTORS FOR FREEDOM COMMITTEE
  - Sub-Series 537-0. Tractors for Freedom Committee
    - General, 1961 (Box 627b, Folder 6)
- Series CXII. NATIONAL TRANSPORTATION POLICY
  - Sub-Series 540-0. National Transportation Policy
    - General, 1962-1963 (Box 627b, Folder 7)
      December 16, 1962-May 1963.
    - General, 1962 (Box 627b, Folder 8)
      November 1961-December 15, 1962.
    - General, 1961 (Box 627b, Folder 9)
      January-October 1961.
- Series CXIII. GRAND PRESIDENT'S CIRCULAR FILE
  - Sub-Series Grand President's Circular File
    - General, 1963 (Box 628, Folder 1)
    - Minutes of Meeting of Grand Executive Council, 1963 (Box 628, Folder 2)
      February 4-7, 1963.
    - General, 1963 (Box 628, Folder 3)
      January-February 1963.
    - Annual Organization Conference, 1963 (Box 628, Folder 4)
      November 27-29, 1963.
    - Minutes of Meeting of Grand Executive Council, 1963 (Box 628, Folder 5)
      August 5-7, 1963.
    - General, 1966 (Box 628, Folder 6)
      November-December 1966.
    - General, 1966 (Box 628, Folder 7)
      August-October 1966.
    - General, 1963 (Box 628, Folder 8)
      July-December 1963.
    - General, 1962 (Box 629, Folder 1)
      1962 May 8
    - General, 1962 (Box 629, Folder 2)
      July-October 1962.
    - General, 1962 (Box 629, Folder 3)
      April-June 1962.
    - General, 1962 (Box 629, Folder 4)
      January-June 1962.
    - General, 1962 (Box 629, Folder 5)
      November-December 1962.
    - General, 1963 (Box 629, Folder 6)
      April-May 1963.
    - General, 1960 (Box 630, Folder 1)
      January-April 1960.
    - General, 1961 (Box 630, Folder 2)
      January-September 1961.
    - General, 1960 (Box 630, Folder 3)
      September-December 1960.
    - General, 1961 (Box 630, Folder 4)
      October-December 1961.
    - General, 1963 (Box 630, Folder 5)
      June-December 1963.
    - General, 1957 (Box 630, Folder 6)
    - General, 1960 (Box 630, Folder 7)
      May-August 1960.
    - General, 1965 (Box 631a, Folder 1)
      January-July 1965.
    - General, 1965 (Box 631a, Folder 2)
      August-December 1965.
    - General, 1964 (Box 631a, Folder 3)
      January-February 1964.
    - Educational Conference, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1964 (Box 631a, Folder 4)
      June 9-11, 1964.
    - General, 1964 (Box 631a, Folder 5)
      March-April 1964.
    - General, 1964 (Box 631a, Folder 6)
      September-December 1964.
    - General, 1964 (Box 631a, Folder 7)
      May 16, 1964-August 1964.
    - Minutes of Meeting of Grand Executive Council, 1964 (Box 631a, Folder 8)
      February 3-6, 1964.
    - General, 1967 (Box 631b, Folder 1)
      January-March 1967.
    - General, 1964 (Box 631b, Folder 2)
      May 1-15, 1964.
    - General, 1967 (Box 631b, Folder 3)
      April-December 1967.
    - General, 1966 (Box 631b, Folder 4)
      January-March 1966.
    - General, 1966 (Box 631b, Folder 5)
      May-July 1966.
    - General, 1966 (Box 631b, Folder 6)